<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Handle customer vehicle enquiries as  P0300 diagnostic trouble code, active recalls available, car still covered by warranty, perks available like free oil change ,Send command for Lock Doors and  Unlock Doors and Start the car and Stop the Car,  customer information for upsell opportunities, update to the user regarding the delay and include a perk  and display the details in bullet point.</description>
    <developerName>Technician_Experience</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Generate_FAQ_From_Automotive_Industry</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>DataCloud_SimulationResult</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Data_Cloud_Survey_Response</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Data_Cloud_Vehicle_Recall_Availblity</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Data_Cloud_Warranty_Coverage</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Data_Cloud_Warranty_Details</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Data_Cloud_Upsell_Opportunities</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>Data_Cloud_Vehicle_Delay_Status</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask What is the meaning of the P0300 diagnostic trouble code?  then run &apos;Generate FAQ From Automotive Industry&apos; action and show exact prompt response 
DO NOT ADD ANY EXTRA WORD ,  DO NOT ASK ANY FOLLOW UP QUESTION AT THE END OF RESPONSE.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer0</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask Are there any active recalls? then call the action &apos;Data Cloud Vehicle Recall Availblity&apos; and pass the current Record Id and say &apos;Here are active recall details for car:&apos; then display details in paragraph.
DO NOT ASK ANYTHING EXTRA.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer1</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer1</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask Is the car still covered by warranty? then call the action &apos;Data Cloud Warranty Details&apos; and pass the current Record Id and say &apos;Here are warranty details:&apos; then display details in paragraph.
DO NOT ADD ANY EXTRA WORD ,  DO NOT ASK ANY FOLLOW UP QUESTION AT THE END OF RESPONSE.

If customer ask Any other perks available like free oil change? then call the action &apos;Data Cloud Warranty Coverage&apos; and pass the current Record Id and say &apos;Here are perk availability details:&apos; then display details in bullet points.
DO NOT ADD ANY EXTRA WORD ,  DO NOT ASK ANY FOLLOW UP QUESTION AT THE END OF RESPONSE.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer2</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer2</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If Customer Say&apos;s Unlock Doors or Lock Doors or Start the car or Stop the car, then run the action &apos;DataCloud-SimulationResult&apos; by passing current Record Id  and pass inputType as Customer&apos;s Command. and say &apos;Here are updates:&apos; and display details in paragraph.
DO NOT ASK ANYTHING EXTRA.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer3</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer3</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If customer ask Send a status update to the user regarding the delay and include a perk, such as a voucher? then call the action &apos;Data Cloud Vehicle Delay Status&apos; and pass the current Record Id and say &apos;Here are updates :&apos; then display details in paragraph.
DO NOT ASK ANYTHING EXTRA.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer4</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer4</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>If Customer ask Tell me more about this customer and what upsell opportunities are there? then run the action &apos;Data Cloud Upsell Opportunities&apos; and pass current Record Id and say &apos;Customer Purchase History &apos; and then display details in paragraph but display only Product Related Material  Name in Hyperlink Format. Do not show any other product related material record details.
DO NOT ASK ANYTHING EXTRA.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_ifcustomer5</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_ifcustomer5</masterLabel>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Technician Experience</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>This job is to help customer to answer queried related to their owned cars   P0300 diagnostic trouble code, active recalls available, car still covered by warranty, perks available like free oil change ,Send command for Lock Doors and  Unlock Doors and and Start the car and Stop the Car,  customer information for upsell opportunities, update to the user regarding the delay and include a perk  and display the details in bullet point</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
